[{"answer": "Totally, especially after the first scandal had already happened.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "You had to say to yourself, this guy is one sick puppy, right?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "You know, he's one tick away from being just a complete perv to be honest with you.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "It's so bizarre, isn't it?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "It's a lack of core values.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Isn't that the problem?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I had an interview last night, I just wanted to talk to you about actually because it was about George Zimmerman, about guns.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "And if Anthony Weiner cannot show the kind of judgment that is necessary, the loyalty to his family that is necessary, what makes you think that he would be the right person to lead the city on New York?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, if we're the ones that supplied the gun and remember, we provided money, not a gun, but if someone is on top of Mr. Zimmerman again repeatedly bashing his head into the concrete, and he acts in self-defense, that's incredible bad luck that he found himself in that situation twice, but we'll sleep soundly.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Where does that leave you if you're the one that supplied the gun?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Every time you point a gun at somebody and you're going to pull the trigger, think, is that life worth $5,000 for a bullet?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "I think it's very important that when somebody is take into custody, that there is some assessment of dangerousness, risk level, because you want more security on a person that poses a risk.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "But actually, he's a very dangerous man, and the obvious question is how could he be in a position to even do this?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, as I said, you need to put people like this in the right facility.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What do you do about this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, my view on this Piers -- and thank you for inviting me on the show.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What is this?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I've give you three.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "To Ben Ferguson, give me one good reason why arming 20 teachers and administrators is a sensible way to reduce gun violence in America?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "No, absolutely not.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "And before I go to Mary Cathryn Ricker, you would presumably by extension of your argument, Ben, you would arm every single teacher in America if you could in every school?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "My huge concern is this idea that for every problem you think you may be solving, there are going to be far more pervasive problems that you're actually creating.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Mary, Mary --", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Are they keeping it locked and loaded?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "You're -- this is where the fear-mongering is exhausting.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Will they have time to go and unlock it?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Well, you actually take the gun.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "Explain to me how you'll do that?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "They wear it on their waist.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Where do the teachers put their guns physically?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Yes, so we're starting in the wrong place.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Mary?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "...of the school district actually said that so -- so first of all, Ben, I actually don't appreciate being accused of not doing my research because I've spent quite a bit of time talking to the...", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "So what do you want to do?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "...that these just are going to happen (ph).", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "So what do you want to do?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "OK, but Ben, very quickly, last point to you and then a final point to Mary, why did Wayne Lapierre as early as 1999 -- why was he so adamant that shouldn't, by his words, that we saw at the top of the segment, there should be no guns at any school in America.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "...and we trust them with our kids, why would we not trust them with this?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Well, evaded is not the word I would use.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, are you surprised that Bradley Manning evaded a conviction for aiding the enemy?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Well, in -- in our lifetime, Daniel Ellsberg, in my opinion, was a whistle-blower.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Where is the line between whistle-blowing and becoming a traitor?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Well, the best way to keep a secret is not to know it.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "So how do you regulate it going forward?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's very important to have a Middle East peace process and having the parties talk even if the prospects of success are -- are not promising, I think is vitally important.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "P.J. Crowley, just finally, instead of just saying (ph) John Kerry through the nine-month goal for Middle East peace talks today, is he being too optimistic do you think?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "It's interesting.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What is your reaction to that reaction?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I don't know anymore.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "What is your wheel house, Brad paisley?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't know, I mean, I don't enough about what she really did.", "docId": "130730pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Was she unfairly vilified, do you think?", "qSentId": 599}]